disabroad.org 2019-09-21

# Privacy Policy | DIS

### Owner information

This website is offered by:

DIS – Study Abroad in Scandinavia  
Vestergade 7  
DK-1456 København K  
Business registration no. in Denmark: DK13058946  
Tel no: +45 33 11 01 44

### Collection of personal data

Personal information is never disclosed to third parties, unless you express consent, and we never collect personal information unless you have given us this information at registration, purchase, or participating in a survey, etc.

### Data Protection Officer

For any GDPR or personal data related inquiries, please contact [dataprotectionofficer@dis.dk](mailto:dataprotectionofficer@dis.dk).

### Cookie Policy

DIS uses cookies for collecting statistics, improving your user experience and for marketing.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small text file stored in your browser to anonymously recognize you on subsequent visits. There is no personal information stored in our cookies and they can not contain viruses.

**For how long are cookies stored**  
Cookies delete themselves after a certain number of months (may vary), but they are renewed after each visit.

**How to delete cookies**  
See instructions here: [http://www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/Default.aspx?page=2 "www.aboutcookies.org")

**How to control  cookies**  
If you do not wish to receive cookies, you can block them.  
See instructions here: [http://www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/Default.aspx?page=1 "www.aboutcookies.org")

**What are cookies used for on our website**  
We use cookies to compile statistics about the use of our site and to help us to recognize users.

**Google Analytics (traffic measurement)**  
You can disable cookies by Google Analytics here: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>
